翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Before we move on from linked lists altogether,
在我们完全离脱离链表之前
let's discuss an obvious limitation
讨论一个明显的限制
that makes our list not so useful in the real world.
这个限制使得我们的 List 在现实世界中没多大用
What is that limitation?
限制是什么？
Well, let's consider here an SSList using class.
考虑这个 SLList 的使用类
It creates an SSList with the number 5
它创建一个包含数字5的 SSList
and adds the number 10.
并添加数字10
And it will all work beautifully and wonderfully.
一切都会工作得漂亮又奇妙
But suppose we wanted to create not a list of integers,
但是假设我们不想创建整数链表
but a list of, say, strings.
而是字符串链表
So I might try and start off with bone, then add thugs.
也许我会初始化为“bone”，添加“thugs”
And if I try running this, well, then I run into an issue.
如果我试着运行它，就会遇到一个问题
String cannot be converted to int.
String 无法转换为 int
And so the fundamental issue we run into
我们遇到的根本问题是
is that an SSList has int nodes, and int nodes have int items.
SSList有 IntNode，IntNode 有 int 项
And therefore if we tried to create an SSList using a string
因此，如果我们尝试使用字符串创建 SSList
or how we try to add to such an SSList using a string,
或者我们尝试将字符串添加到这样的 SSList 中
we will get an error.
我们会得到错误
You cannot do this.
你不能这么做
You cannot take strings and convert them into integers.
不能将字符串转换为整数
That's the ultimate trouble.
这才是最大的麻烦
So how do we fix that?
怎么解决呢？
Well, the lamest possible way we can fix it
能解决的最差办法是
is we could make an entirely new SSList class,
我们可以创建一个全新的 SSList 类
like string SSList
比如字符串 SSList
and then do a Find and Replace for int everywhere, and oh boy,
然后对各处的 int 进行查找和替换，天哪
and that would be a terrible idea, obviously.
显然这将是一个糟糕的想法
So the current approach in modern Java
目前现代 Java 的做法是
is to make SSList a parametrized--
让 SSList 参数化
well, we can parametrize the type that SSList will take.
我们可以参数化 SSList 将采用的类型
What does that possibly mean?
这是什么意思？
OK, so what I'm going to do is I'm going to add new little angled braces here right after the name SSList.
我将在 SLList 后面添加小尖括号
And here I'm going to pick any old string, something arbitrary like-- LochNess.
在这里我将挑选老旧的字符串，比如 LochNess
And that's just going to act as a placeholder for a type that is not decided at the time SSList was created.
这将充当在创建 SSList 时未决定类型的占位符
So instead of an int item, we're going to have a LochNess.
因此我们将使用 LochNess ，而不是 int
Instead of creating a IntNode, we're going to say public IntNode.
不再创建 IntNode，而是...
And we need to provide a LochNess.
提供一个 LochNess
IntNode is probably not a great name,
IntNode 可能不是一个好名字
since it's no longer IntNode.
因为它不再是 IntNode
So let's do a Find and Replace on that too.
因此对其进行查找和替换
No IntNode, we'll just call this thing StuffNode.
没有 IntNode，我们就称它为 StuffNode
just to emphasize it still has stuff in it.
只是为了强调它还有东西在里面
And then I'm going to keep working my way through.
然后我会继续努力完成目标
So when we create an SSList list now
当我们现在创建 SSList 时
I'll take LochNesses instead of ints.
使用 LochNess 而不是 int
We add LochNesses.
添加 LochNess
We return LochNesses.
返回 LochNess
We add LochNesses.
添加 LochNess
And at that point we're all done.
我们都做完了
So the important part, the main thing I changed other than just the name of IntNode,
重要的是，除了更改 IntNode 的名称之外
is that I added LochNess here.
我在这里添加了 LochNess
This will compile.
进行编译
And now an SSList, and then it won't run,
现在 SLList 不会运行了
because there's no main method.
因为没有 main 方法
But it compiles.
但它会编译
And it should work fine.
而且应该编译得很好
How do we actually use one of these things?
我们如何在实际中使用呢？
Now if we wanted to make an SSList,
现在如果我们想做一个 SSList
we're going to now need to specify a type when we create an SSList.
需要在创建 SSList 时指定一个类型
And we'll do it with the angled braces.
使用尖角括号
And so to do that, I'll say I want an SSList of strings.
要做到这一点，需要 String 类型的 SLList
So here we go.
我们开始吧
We say, I would like to declare an SSList of string variable and instantiate an SSList of strings.
声明一个字符串的 SSList 并实例化一个字符串的 SSList
And now when we try running this,
现在我们试着运行
everything should work fine.
一切都应该运行得很好
So there it went.
成功了
It worked.
真灵
And so what's going on here is that whenever we instantiate an SSList,
这里发生的事情是，每当我们实例化 SSList 时
this string right here will get substituted everywhere in for LochNess.
这里的 String 将被各处的 LochNess 替换
So it's basically a type variable or a type parameter.
它基本上是一个类型变量或类型参数
And so it can get a little confusing,
这可能会让人有点困惑
and we're not going to talk a lot about it right now.
我们现在不会谈论太多
I just want you to know the basics.
只想让你知道最基本的事情
Now in even more modern Java, it is no longer necessary to specify the type on the instantiation side.
在更现代的 Java 中，不再需要在实例化方面指定类型
So I'm going to delete that.
所以我要把它删除
And this too will work.
这也会奏效
So let's just summarize there, and later in the course
我们在这里总结一下，以后课程中也是
we're going to dig a lot more deeply into this issue.
我们将更深入地挖掘这个问题
But to summarize what we've got here,
但先总结一下
is we can defer type selection until later,
我们可以将推迟类型选择
until we've declared a variable or until we've instantiated a variable.
直到我们声明了一个变量或实例化了一个变量
And to do that we pick any arbitrary string.
要做到这一点，我们挑选任意字符串
And in the class that we're creating,
在我们创建的类中
we just put it right after the name.
只是把它放在名字的后面
And then when we want to use it,
想要使用它的时候
we make sure that we specify the type we want  when we're declaring, and optionally when we're instantiating.
我们要确保在声明或实例化时指定想要的类型
So again, we'll go into this in so much more detail.
再说一遍，我们会更详细地讨论
There's a lot of little details that can be confusing.
有很多小细节可能会让人感到困惑
But these are the rules of thumb you'll need for project 1,
但这些是你在项目一中需要的经验法则
where you're going to build a generic list.
你将会构建一个泛型链表
So in the Java file where you implement your data structure,
因此在你实现数据结构的 Java 文件中
this side where you're building the actual thing,
当你构建实际的东西
you'll specify your generic type only once at the very top of the file, right there, BleepBlorp.
只需在文件的顶部指定一次你的泛型类型，BleepBlorp
And it's specified inside of these angled braces.
它在这些尖括号里指定
You can use it elsewhere, but you will only specify it once.
你可以在其他地方使用，但只需指定一次
And then in Java files that use your data structure,
然后在你使用数据结构的 Java 文件中
you'll specify the desired type just once.
你只需指定一次所需类型
You'll do it whenever you declare the variable,
你可以在声明变量时执行
and then use the empty diamond operator during instantiation.
然后在实例化期间使用空的菱形运算符
I mean you can also write out doubles.
你也可以写两次
You could technically use it twice.
从技术上讲可以写两次
But this will make your code look more like what you're likely to see in the real world.
但是这样会使你的代码更接近于实际
And when you're actually declaring or instantiating your data structure,
而当你实际声明或实例化你的数据结构时
whenever you're putting something inside of these braces,
每次你把东西放进括号
you want to make sure that you use capital I integer,
要确保使用大写 I 的 Integer
capital D double, and so forth.
大写 D 的 Double，以此类推
So you use the reference type corresponding to each of the primitive types.
你要使用与每个原始类型相对应的引用类型
So that will give you as much as you need on project 1.
这些是你在项目一中所需的
And they'll be a couple of little tiny gotchas
它们会有几个小问题
that will be mentioned in the project 1 FAQ.
将在项目一的 FAQ 中提到
And we'll get into generics more somewhat later.
稍后我们会更深入地讨论泛型
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）